<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE pagecontents SYSTEM "termsandconditions.dtd">
<pagecontents>
<pagecontent lang="de"><![CDATA[<h2>Teilnahme am Spiel</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Es ist nur ein Benutzerkonto pro Mitspieler erlaubt.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Das Benutzerkonto darf nicht an Dritte weitergegeben werden. Vermuteter Missbrauch des eigenen Kontos muss unverzüglich gemeldet werden.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Der frei wählbare Benutzername darf keine Schutzrechte Dritter verletzen. Insbesondere dürfen keine Namen von Vereinen oder Spieler aus der realen Fußballwelt benutzt werden.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Die Mitgliedschaft kann jederzeit und ohne Angabe von Gründen von beiden Vertragsparteien gekündigt werden.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Der Betreiber behält sich das Recht vor, diese Teilnahmebestimmungen jederzeit zu Ändern oder zu ergänzen.
<h2>Datenschutz</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Der Betreiber speichert personenbezogene Daten nur soweit rechtlich zulässig und sofern sie für den Spielbetrieb nötig sind. Darunter fallen unter anderem die IP-Adresse des Nutzers und seine E-Mail-Adresse.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Der Nutzer hat jederzeit das Recht, Art und Umfang seiner gespeicherten Daten unentgeltlich bei dem Betreiber zu erfragen.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Für den Betrieb der Webseite ist es erforderlich, sogenannte "Cookies" auf Ihrem Gerät zu speichern. Dies sind kleine Textdateien, die Informationen über Sie zur Wiedererkennung für das System enthalten.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="en"><![CDATA[<h2>Game Membership</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Only one user account per member is permitted.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> The user account must not be accessible by any third person. Assumed abuse must be reported immediately.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> The user name which you may choose must not violate any proprietary right. In particular you are not allowed to use names of clubs or players from the real football world.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> The membership can be cancelled by both parties at any time and without giving reasons.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> The provider reserves the right to change these terms and conditions at any time.
<h2>Data Privacy</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> The provider stores personal information as long as it is permitted by law and required to run the service. These include, but are not limited to, the user's IP and e-mail address.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> The user is entitled to ask, free of charge, for information about which kind and amount of data about him is stored by the provider.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> For running this website it is required to store so called "Cookies" on your computer. These are small text files containing information which help the system identifying your user account.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="es"><![CDATA[<h2>Afiliación al juego	</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Sólo se permite una cuenta de usuario por miembro.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> La cuenta de usuario no debe ser accesible por terceros. Los supuestos abusos deben denunciarse inmediatamente.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> El nombre de usuario que elija no debe violar ningún derecho de propiedad. En particular, no está permitido utilizar nombres de clubes o jugadores del mundo del fútbol real.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> La afiliación puede ser cancelada por ambas partes en cualquier momento y sin indicar los motivos.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> El proveedor se reserva el derecho a modificar estas condiciones en cualquier momento.
<h2>Protección de datos</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> El proveedor almacena datos personales mientras la ley lo permita y sea necesario para el funcionamiento del servicio. Estos datos incluyen, entre otros, la IP y la dirección de correo electrónico del usuario.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> El usuario tiene derecho a solicitar, de forma gratuita, información sobre qué tipo y cantidad de datos sobre él almacena el proveedor.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Para el funcionamiento de este sitio web es necesario almacenar en su ordenador las denominadas "Cookies". Se trata de pequeños archivos de texto que contienen información que ayuda al sistema a identificar su cuenta de usuario.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="dk"><![CDATA[<h2>Medlemskab af spil</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Der er kun tilladt én brugerkonto pr. medlem.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Brugerkontoen må ikke være tilgængelig for nogen tredjeperson. Formodet misbrug skal straks indberettes.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Det brugernavn, som du måtte vælge, må ikke krænke nogen ejendomsrettighed. Du må navnlig ikke bruge navne på klubber eller spillere fra den virkelige fodboldverden.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Medlemskabet kan til enhver tid og uden begrundelse opsiges af begge parter.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Udbyderen forbeholder sig ret til at ændre disse vilkår og betingelser til enhver tid.
<h2>Databeskyttelse</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Udbyderen gemmer personlige oplysninger, så længe det er tilladt i henhold til loven og nødvendigt for at drive tjenesten. Disse omfatter, men er ikke begrænset til, brugerens IP-adresse og e-mailadresse.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Brugeren har ret til gratis at anmode om oplysninger om, hvilken type og mængde af data om ham, der opbevares af udbyderen.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> For at kunne drive dette websted er det nødvendigt at gemme såkaldte "cookies" på din computer. Det er små tekstfiler med oplysninger, som hjælper systemet med at identificere din brugerkonto.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="ee"><![CDATA[<h2>Mängu liikmelisus</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Ühe liikme kohta on lubatud ainult üks kasutajakonto.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Kasutajakonto ei tohi olla kättesaadav kolmandatele isikutele. Oletatavast kuritarvitamisest tuleb viivitamatult teatada.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Teie poolt valitud kasutajanimi ei tohi rikkuda ühtegi omandiõigust. Eelkõige ei ole lubatud kasutada klubide või mängijate nimesid reaalsest jalgpallimaailmast.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Mõlemad osapooled võivad liikmeksoleku igal ajal ja ilma põhjendusi esitamata tühistada.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Teenusepakkuja jätab endale õiguse neid tingimusi igal ajal muuta.
<h2>Andmekaitse</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Teenusepakkuja säilitab isikuandmeid seni, kuni see on seadusega lubatud ja teenuse osutamiseks vajalik. Nende hulka kuuluvad muu hulgas kasutaja IP- ja e-posti aadress.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Kasutajal on õigus küsida tasuta teavet selle kohta, millist liiki ja millises mahus andmeid teenusepakkuja tema kohta säilitab.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Selle veebisaidi käitamiseks on vaja salvestada teie arvutisse nn küpsiseid. Need on väikesed tekstifailid, mis sisaldavad teavet, mis aitab süsteemil teie kasutajakontot tuvastada.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="fi"><![CDATA[<h2>Pelin jäsenyys</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Vain yksi käyttäjätili per jäsen on sallittu.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Käyttäjätiliin ei saa olla pääsyä kolmannella henkilöllä. Oletetusta väärinkäytöstä on ilmoitettava välittömästi.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Valitsemasi käyttäjätunnus ei saa loukata mitään omistusoikeuksia. Erityisesti et saa käyttää todellisen jalkapallomaailman seurojen tai pelaajien nimiä.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Molemmat osapuolet voivat peruuttaa jäsenyyden milloin tahansa ja ilman perusteluja.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Palveluntarjoaja pidättää oikeuden muuttaa näitä ehtoja milloin tahansa.
<h2>Tietosuoja</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Palveluntarjoaja säilyttää henkilötietoja niin kauan kuin laki sallii ja palvelun ylläpitäminen sitä edellyttää. Näitä ovat muun muassa käyttäjän IP-osoite ja sähköpostiosoite.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Käyttäjällä on oikeus pyytää maksutta tietoja siitä, millaisia ja kuinka paljon tietoja palveluntarjoaja tallentaa hänestä.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Tämän verkkosivuston käyttäminen edellyttää niin sanottujen "evästeiden" tallentamista tietokoneellesi. Nämä ovat pieniä tekstitiedostoja, jotka sisältävät tietoja, jotka auttavat järjestelmää tunnistamaan käyttäjätilisi.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="fr"><![CDATA[<h2>Adhésion au jeu</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Un seul compte utilisateur par membre est autorisé.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Le compte d'utilisateur ne doit pas être accessible par une tierce personne. Les abus présumés doivent être signalés immédiatement.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Le nom d'utilisateur que vous pouvez choisir ne doit violer aucun droit de propriété. En particulier, vous n'êtes pas autorisé à utiliser des noms de clubs ou de joueurs du monde réel du football.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> L'adhésion peut être annulée par les deux parties à tout moment et sans indication de motifs.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Le fournisseur se réserve le droit de modifier ces conditions à tout moment.
<h2>Confidentialité des données	</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Le fournisseur conserve les informations personnelles aussi longtemps que la loi l'autorise et que cela est nécessaire au fonctionnement du service. Il s'agit notamment, mais pas exclusivement, de l'adresse IP et de l'adresse électronique de l'utilisateur.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> L'utilisateur a le droit de demander gratuitement des informations sur le type et la quantité de données le concernant qui sont stockées par le fournisseur.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Pour faire fonctionner ce site web, il est nécessaire de stocker des "cookies" sur votre ordinateur. Il s'agit de petits fichiers texte contenant des informations qui aident le système à identifier votre compte utilisateur.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="id"><![CDATA[<h2>Keanggotaan Permainan</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Hanya satu akun pengguna per anggota yang diizinkan.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Akun pengguna tidak boleh diakses oleh orang ketiga. Dugaan penyalahgunaan harus segera dilaporkan.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Nama pengguna yang dapat Anda pilih tidak boleh melanggar hak kepemilikan apa pun. Secara khusus Anda tidak diperbolehkan menggunakan nama klub atau pemain dari dunia sepak bola yang sebenarnya.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Keanggotaan dapat dibatalkan oleh kedua belah pihak kapan saja dan tanpa memberikan alasan.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Penyedia berhak untuk mengubah syarat dan ketentuan ini kapan saja.
<h2>Privasi Data</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Penyedia menyimpan informasi pribadi selama diizinkan oleh hukum dan diperlukan untuk menjalankan layanan. Ini termasuk, tetapi tidak terbatas pada, IP dan alamat email pengguna.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Pengguna berhak untuk meminta, secara gratis, informasi tentang jenis dan jumlah data tentang dirinya yang disimpan oleh penyedia.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Untuk menjalankan situs web ini, diperlukan untuk menyimpan apa yang disebut "Cookies" di komputer Anda. Ini adalah file teks kecil yang berisi informasi yang membantu sistem mengidentifikasi akun pengguna Anda.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="it"><![CDATA[<h2>Iscrizione al gioco</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> È consentito un solo account utente per ogni membro.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> L'account utente non deve essere accessibile a terzi. I presunti abusi devono essere segnalati immediatamente.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Il nome utente che l'utente può scegliere non deve violare alcun diritto di proprietà. In particolare, non è consentito utilizzare nomi di club o giocatori del mondo del calcio reale.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> L'iscrizione può essere annullata da entrambe le parti in qualsiasi momento e senza fornire motivazioni.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Il fornitore si riserva il diritto di modificare questi termini e condizioni in qualsiasi momento.
<h2>Privacy dei dati</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Il fornitore conserva i dati personali per tutto il tempo consentito dalla legge e necessario per la gestione del servizio. Questi includono, ma non solo, l'IP e l'indirizzo e-mail dell'utente.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> L'utente ha il diritto di richiedere gratuitamente informazioni sul tipo e sulla quantità di dati che lo riguardano memorizzati dal provider.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Per il funzionamento di questo sito web è necessario memorizzare i cosiddetti "cookie" sul computer dell'utente. Si tratta di piccoli file di testo contenenti informazioni che aiutano il sistema a identificare il vostro account utente.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="lv"><![CDATA[<h2>Daliba spele</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Katram dalibniekam ir atlauts tikai viens lietotaja konts.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Lietotaja kontam nedrikst pieklut neviena treša persona. Par iespejamu launpratigu izmantošanu ir nekavejoties jazino.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Jusu izveletais lietotajvards nedrikst parkapt ipašumtiesibas. Jo ipaši nav atlauts izmantot realas futbola pasaules klubu vai speletaju nosaukumus.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Abas puses jebkura laika var atcelt dalibu, nenoradot iemeslus.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Pakalpojumu sniedzejs patur tiesibas jebkura laika mainit šos noteikumus un nosacijumus.
<h2>Datu konfidencialitate</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Pakalpojuma sniedzejs glaba personas datus tik ilgi, cik to atlauj likums un cik tas ir nepieciešams pakalpojuma sniegšanai. Tie ietver, bet neaprobežojas ar lietotaja IP un e-pasta adresi.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Lietotajam ir tiesibas bez maksas pieprasit informaciju par to, kadus datus un kada apjoma par vinu glaba pakalpojumu sniedzejs.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Šis timekla vietnes darbibai jusu datora ir nepieciešams saglabat ta sauktas "sikdatnes". Tie ir nelieli teksta faili, kas satur informaciju, kura palidz sistemai identificet jusu lietotaja kontu.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="lt"><![CDATA[<h2>Žaidimo naryste</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Vienam nariui leidžiama tureti tik viena naudotojo paskyra.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Naudotojo paskyra negali buti prieinama jokiam treciajam asmeniui. Apie numanoma piktnaudžiavima reikia nedelsiant pranešti.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Vartotojo vardas, kuri galite pasirinkti, neturi pažeisti jokiu nuosavybes teisiu. Visu pirma jums neleidžiama naudoti klubu ar žaideju pavadinimu iš realaus futbolo pasaulio.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Naryste abi šalys gali bet kada nutraukti nenurodydamos priežasciu.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Paslaugu teikejas pasilieka teise bet kuriuo metu pakeisti šias salygas.
<h2>Duomenu privatumas</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Teikejas saugo asmenine informacija tol, kol tai leidžia istatymai ir kol ji reikalinga paslaugai teikti. Tai, be kita ko, yra naudotojo IP ir el. pašto adresas.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Naudotojas turi teise nemokamai paprašyti informacijos apie tai, kokios rušies ir kiek duomenu apie ji saugo paslaugu teikejas.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Kad ši svetaine veiktu, jusu kompiuteryje butina išsaugoti vadinamuosius "slapukus". Tai nedideli tekstiniai failai, kuriuose yra informacijos, padedancios sistemai identifikuoti jusu naudotojo paskyra.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="nl"><![CDATA[<h2>Lidmaatschap van het spel</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Slechts één gebruikersaccount per lid is toegestaan.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Het gebruikersaccount mag niet toegankelijk zijn voor derden. Vermeend misbruik moet onmiddellijk worden gemeld.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> De gebruikersnaam die je mag kiezen mag geen inbreuk maken op enig eigendomsrecht. Het is met name niet toegestaan namen van clubs of spelers uit de echte voetbalwereld te gebruiken.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Het lidmaatschap kan door beide partijen te allen tijde en zonder opgaaf van redenen worden opgezegd.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> De aanbieder behoudt zich het recht voor deze voorwaarden te allen tijde te wijzigen.
<h2>Privacy van gegevens</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> De aanbieder bewaart persoonlijke informatie zolang dit wettelijk is toegestaan en nodig is om de dienst te kunnen uitvoeren. Deze omvatten, maar zijn niet beperkt tot, het IP- en e-mailadres van de gebruiker.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> De gebruiker heeft het recht om gratis informatie te vragen over welke soort en hoeveelheid gegevens over hem door de provider worden opgeslagen.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Voor de werking van deze website is het nodig zogenaamde "Cookies" op uw computer op te slaan. Dit zijn kleine tekstbestanden met informatie waarmee het systeem uw gebruikersaccount kan identificeren.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="pl"><![CDATA[<h2>Czlonkostwo w grze</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Dozwolone jest tylko jedno konto uzytkownika na jednego czlonka.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Konto uzytkownika nie moze byc dostepne dla osób trzecich. Domniemane naduzycia musza byc natychmiast zglaszane.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Nazwa uzytkownika, która mozesz wybrac, nie moze naruszac zadnych praw wlasnosci. W szczególnosci nie wolno uzywac nazw klubów lub zawodników z prawdziwego swiata pilki noznej.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Czlonkostwo moze zostac anulowane przez obie strony w dowolnym momencie i bez podania przyczyn.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Oferent zastrzega sobie prawo do zmiany tych warunków w kazdej chwili.
<h2>Ochrona danych osobowych</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Oferent przechowuje dane osobowe tak dlugo, jak dlugo jest to dozwolone przez prawo i wymagane do prowadzenia serwisu. Naleza do nich miedzy innymi IP i adres e-mail uzytkownika.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Uzytkownik ma prawo do bezplatnego zazadania informacji o tym, jakiego rodzaju i w jakiej ilosci dane o nim sa przechowywane przez oferenta.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Do prowadzenia niniejszej strony internetowej wymagane jest przechowywanie na komputerze uzytkownika tzw. plików "Cookies". Sa to male pliki tekstowe zawierajace informacje, które pomagaja systemowi w identyfikacji konta uzytkownika.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="pt"><![CDATA[<h2>Adesão ao jogo</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Só é permitida uma conta de utilizador por membro.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> A conta de utilizador não deve ser acessível por qualquer terceira pessoa. Os abusos presumidos devem ser denunciados imediatamente.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> O nome de utilizador que o utilizador pode escolher não deve violar qualquer direito de propriedade. Em particular, não é permitida a utilização de nomes de clubes ou jogadores do mundo real do futebol.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> A adesão pode ser cancelada por ambas as partes em qualquer altura e sem indicação dos motivos.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> O fornecedor reserva-se o direito de alterar estes termos e condições em qualquer altura.
<h2>Privacidade de dados</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> O fornecedor armazena informações pessoais desde que seja permitido por lei e exigido para a execução do serviço. Estas incluem, mas não estão limitadas ao IP e endereço de correio electrónico do utilizador.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> O utilizador tem o direito de pedir, gratuitamente, informações sobre que tipo e quantidade de dados a seu respeito são armazenados pelo fornecedor.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Para executar este website, é necessário armazenar os chamados "Cookies" no seu computador. Estes são pequenos ficheiros de texto que contêm informações que ajudam o sistema a identificar a sua conta de utilizador.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="br"><![CDATA[<h2>Afiliação a jogos</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Apenas uma conta de usuário por membro é permitida.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> A conta de usuário não deve ser acessível por qualquer terceira pessoa. Presume-se que abusos devem ser reportados imediatamente.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> O nome de usuário que você pode escolher não deve violar nenhum direito de propriedade. Em particular, não é permitido usar nomes de clubes ou jogadores do mundo real do futebol.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> A associação pode ser cancelada por ambas as partes a qualquer momento e sem dar razões.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> O provedor se reserva o direito de alterar estes termos e condições a qualquer momento.
<h2>Privacidade dos dados</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> O fornecedor armazena informações pessoais desde que seja permitido por lei e exigido para executar o serviço. Estas incluem, mas não estão limitadas ao IP e endereço de e-mail do usuário.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> O usuário tem o direito de pedir, gratuitamente, informações sobre que tipo e quantidade de dados a seu respeito são armazenados pelo provedor.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Para rodar este site é necessário armazenar os chamados "Cookies" em seu computador. Estes são pequenos arquivos de texto contendo informações que ajudam o sistema a identificar sua conta de usuário.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="ro"><![CDATA[<h2>Apartenen?a la joc</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Este permis un singur cont de utilizator pentru fiecare membru.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Contul de utilizator nu trebuie sa fie accesibil unei ter?e persoane. Presupusul abuz trebuie raportat imediat.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Numele de utilizator pe care îl pute?i alege nu trebuie sa încalce niciun drept de proprietate. În special, nu ave?i voie sa folosi?i nume de cluburi sau jucatori din lumea reala a fotbalului.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Calitatea de membru poate fi anulata de ambele par?i în orice moment ?i fara a oferi motive.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Furnizorul î?i rezerva dreptul de a modifica ace?ti termeni ?i condi?ii în orice moment.
<h2>Confiden?ialitatea datelor</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Furnizorul stocheaza informa?iile personale atât timp cât este permis de lege ?i este necesar pentru func?ionarea serviciului. Acestea includ, dar nu se limiteaza la, IP-ul ?i adresa de e-mail a utilizatorului.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Utilizatorul are dreptul de a solicita, în mod gratuit, informa?ii cu privire la tipul ?i cantitatea de date despre el stocate de catre furnizor.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Pentru func?ionarea acestui site web este necesara stocarea pe computerul dumneavoastra a a?a-numitelor "cookie-uri". Acestea sunt mici fi?iere text care con?in informa?ii care ajuta sistemul sa identifice contul dumneavoastra de utilizator.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="se"><![CDATA[<h2>Medlemskap i spelet</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Endast ett användarkonto per medlem är tillåtet.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Användarkontot får inte vara tillgängligt för någon tredje person. Antaget missbruk måste rapporteras omedelbart.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Det användarnamn som du får välja får inte kränka någon äganderätt. I synnerhet är det inte tillåtet att använda namn på klubbar eller spelare från den verkliga fotbollsvärlden.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Medlemskapet kan sägas upp av båda parter när som helst och utan motivering.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Leverantören förbehåller sig rätten att ändra dessa villkor när som helst.
<h2>Dataskydd</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Leverantören lagrar personuppgifter så länge som det är tillåtet enligt lag och krävs för att driva tjänsten. Dessa inkluderar, men är inte begränsade till, användarens IP-adress och e-postadress.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Användaren har rätt att kostnadsfritt begära information om vilken typ och mängd av uppgifter om honom som leverantören lagrar.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> För att denna webbplats ska fungera krävs det att så kallade "cookies" lagras på din dator. Detta är små textfiler som innehåller information som hjälper systemet att identifiera ditt användarkonto.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="sk"><![CDATA[<h2>Clenstvo v hre</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Každý clen má povolené len jedno používatelské konto.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Používatelské konto nesmie byt prístupné žiadnej tretej osobe. Predpokladané zneužitie je potrebné okamžite nahlásit.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Používatelské meno, ktoré si môžete zvolit, nesmie porušovat žiadne vlastnícke právo. Najmä nesmiete používat názvy klubov alebo hrácov zo skutocného futbalového sveta.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Clenstvo môžu obe strany kedykolvek zrušit bez udania dôvodu.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Poskytovatel si vyhradzuje právo kedykolvek zmenit tieto podmienky.
<h2>Ochrana osobných údajov</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Poskytovatel uchováva osobné údaje tak dlho, ako to povoluje zákon a ako je to potrebné na prevádzku služby. Patria medzi ne okrem iného IP adresa a e-mailová adresa používatela.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Používatel má právo bezplatne požiadat o informácie o tom, aký druh a množstvo údajov o nom poskytovatel uchováva.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Na prevádzkovanie tejto webovej stránky je potrebné uložit do vášho pocítaca tzv. Ide o malé textové súbory obsahujúce informácie, ktoré pomáhajú systému identifikovat vaše používatelské konto.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="si"><![CDATA[<h2>Clanstvo v igri</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Na clana je dovoljen samo en uporabniški racun.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Uporabniški racun ne sme biti dostopen tretji osebi. Domnevno zlorabo je treba takoj prijaviti.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Uporabniško ime, ki ga lahko izberete, ne sme kršiti nobene lastninske pravice. Zlasti ni dovoljeno uporabljati imen klubov ali igralcev iz resnicnega nogometnega sveta.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Clanstvo lahko obe strani kadar koli prekliceta brez navedbe razlogov.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Ponudnik si pridržuje pravico, da te pogoje kadar koli spremeni.
<h2>Zasebnost podatkov</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Ponudnik hrani osebne podatke, dokler je to dovoljeno z zakonom in potrebno za izvajanje storitve. Ti podatki med drugim vkljucujejo uporabnikov IP in e-poštni naslov.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Uporabnik ima pravico brezplacno zahtevati informacije o tem, katere vrste in kolicino podatkov o njem hrani ponudnik.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Za delovanje tega spletnega mesta je treba na vašem racunalniku shraniti tako imenovane "piškotke". To so majhne besedilne datoteke z informacijami, ki pomagajo sistemu prepoznati vaš uporabniški racun.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="cz"><![CDATA[<h2>Clenství ve hre</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Každý clen má povolen pouze jeden uživatelský úcet.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> K uživatelskému úctu nesmí mít prístup žádná tretí osoba. Predpokládané zneužití musí být okamžite nahlášeno.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Uživatelské jméno, které si mužete zvolit, nesmí porušovat žádná vlastnická práva. Zejména není dovoleno používat jména klubu nebo hrácu ze skutecného fotbalového sveta.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Clenství mohou obe strany kdykoli a bez udání duvodu zrušit.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Poskytovatel si vyhrazuje právo tyto podmínky kdykoli zmenit.
<h2>Ochrana osobních údaju</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Poskytovatel uchovává osobní údaje tak dlouho, dokud je to povoleno zákonem a nutné k provozování služby. Patrí mezi ne mimo jiné IP adresa a e-mailová adresa uživatele.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Uživatel je oprávnen bezplatne požádat o informace o tom, jaký druh a množství údaju o nem poskytovatel uchovává.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Pro provoz techto webových stránek je nutné ukládat na vašem pocítaci tzv. soubory cookie. Jedná se o malé textové soubory obsahující informace, které pomáhají systému identifikovat váš uživatelský úcet.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="tr"><![CDATA[<h2>Oyun Üyeligi</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Üye basina sadece bir kullanici hesabina izin verilir.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Kullanici hesabina herhangi bir üçüncü kisi tarafindan erisilememelidir. Varsayilan kötüye kullanim derhal bildirilmelidir.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Seçebileceginiz kullanici adi herhangi bir mülkiyet hakkini ihlal etmemelidir. Özellikle gerçek futbol dünyasindan kulüplerin veya oyuncularin isimlerini kullanmaniza izin verilmez.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Üyelik her iki tarafça da herhangi bir zamanda ve sebep gösterilmeksizin iptal edilebilir.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Saglayici, bu hüküm ve kosullari istedigi zaman degistirme hakkini sakli tutar.
<h2>Veri Gizliligi</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Saglayici, kisisel bilgileri yasalarin izin verdigi ve hizmeti yürütmek için gerekli oldugu sürece saklar. Bunlar, kullanicinin IP'sini ve e-posta adresini içerir, ancak bunlarla sinirli degildir.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Kullanici, kendisi hakkinda hangi tür ve miktarda verinin saglayici tarafindan saklandigi hakkinda ücretsiz olarak bilgi isteme hakkina sahiptir.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Bu web sitesinin çalismasi için bilgisayarinizda "Çerezler" olarak adlandirilan verilerin depolanmasi gerekmektedir. Bunlar, sistemin kullanici hesabinizi tanimlamasina yardimci olan bilgileri içeren küçük metin dosyalaridir.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="hu"><![CDATA[<h2>Játék tagság</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> Tagonként csak egy felhasználói fiók engedélyezett.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> A felhasználói fiókhoz harmadik személy nem férhet hozzá. A feltételezett visszaéléseket azonnal jelenteni kell.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i>	Az Ön által választott felhasználónév nem sérthet semmilyen tulajdonjogot. Különösen tilos a valós futballvilágból származó klubok vagy játékosok neveit használni.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> A tagságot mindkét fél bármikor, indoklás nélkül felmondhatja.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> A szolgáltató fenntartja a jogot, hogy bármikor megváltoztassa ezeket a feltételeket.
<h2>Adatvédelem</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> A szolgáltató a személyes adatokat addig tárolja, amíg azt a törvény megengedi és a szolgáltatás muködtetéséhez szükséges. Ezek közé tartozik többek között a felhasználó IP címe és e-mail címe.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> A felhasználó jogosult ingyenesen tájékoztatást kérni arról, hogy a szolgáltató milyen típusú és mennyiségu adatot tárol róla.
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i> A weboldal muködtetéséhez szükséges az úgynevezett "sütik" tárolása az Ön számítógépén. Ezek olyan kis szöveges fájlok, amelyek olyan információkat tartalmaznak, amelyek segítenek a rendszernek az Ön felhasználói fiókjának azonosításában.]]></pagecontent>
<pagecontent lang="jp"><![CDATA[<h2>ゲーム会員</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i>ユーザーアカウントは、会員1名につき1つだけ使用できます。
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i>ユーザーアカウントは、第三者がアクセスできないようにする必要があります。虐待と思われる場合は、直ちに報告してください。
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i>お客様が選択されるユーザーネームは、いかなる財産的権利も侵害しないものでなければなりません。特に、現実のサッカー界にあるクラブ名や選手名を使用することはできません。
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i>会員資格の取り消しは、両者共にいつでも理由なく行うことができるものとします。
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i>提供者は、本規約を随時変更する権利を有します。
<h2>データプライバシー</h2>
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i>提供者は、法令で認められ、かつサービスの運営に必要な限りにおいて、個人情報を保管します。これには、ユーザーのIPおよび電子メールアドレスが含まれますが、これらに限定されるものではありません。
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i>ユーザーは、プロバイダが保存している自分に関するデータの種類と量について、無料で情報を求める権利を有します。
<i class="icon-chevron-sign-right"></i>本ウェブサイトの運営には、お客様のコンピュータにクッキーと呼ばれるデータを保存することが必要です。これらは、システムがあなたのユーザー・アカウントを識別するのに役立つ情報を含む小さなテキスト・ファイルです。]]></pagecontent>
</pagecontents>